{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T20:56:40.199326", "session_summary": [{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T20:55:08.208606", "question": "What animal says 'meow'?", "answer": "the cat", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T20:55:27.108946", "question": "What color is the sky on a clear day?", "answer": "blue", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T20:55:47.420595", "question": "What did you have for breakfast today?", "answer": "bro eggs", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T20:56:12.213586", "question": "What room are you in right now?", "answer": "in class", "is_correct": false}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T20:56:26.917626", "question": "What room are you in right now?", "answer": "i'm in the kitchen", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T20:56:40.139456", "question": "What were you doing yesterday at 3 PM?", "answer": "sleeping", "is_correct": true}], "final_score": 5}
{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:06:18.068082", "session_summary": [{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:04:43.165157", "question": "What animal says 'meow'?", "answer": "a cat", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:04:59.904728", "question": "What color is the sky on a clear day?", "answer": "the sky is blue", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:05:13.000244", "question": "What did you have for breakfast today?", "answer": "lasagna", "is_correct": false}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:05:31.984948", "question": "What did you have for breakfast today?", "answer": "eggs", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:05:44.840491", "question": "What room are you in right now?", "answer": "i'm in the kitchen", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:06:18.002866", "question": "What were you doing yesterday at 3 PM?", "answer": "do you know what sleeping and sleeping we did it already", "is_correct": true}], "final_score": 5}
{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:08:37.920308", "session_summary": [], "final_score": 0}
{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:23:05.330498", "session_summary": [{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:20:23.180066", "question": "Can you describe the last time you went to the grocery store?", "answer": "it's not even", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:20:40.465515", "question": "Can you describe the route from your bedroom to the bathroom?", "answer": "it's all straight", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:20:58.297542", "question": "Tell me the steps to call someone using your phone.", "answer": "turn on the phone type in your", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:21:14.376000", "question": "What year did you get married or graduate?", "answer": "2024", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:21:30.346117", "question": "Can you name 3 people you saw in the past two days?", "answer": "mom dad and sarah", "is_correct": false}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:22:13.457178", "question": "Can you name 3 people you saw in the past two days?", "answer": "mom", "is_correct": false}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:22:30.761180", "question": "Can you name 3 people you saw in the past two days?", "answer": "mom dad emily", "is_correct": false}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:23:05.272721", "question": "Can you name 3 people you saw in the past two days?", "answer": "tell us i", "is_correct": true}], "final_score": 5}
{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:32:06.036146", "session_summary": [{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:30:57.959013", "question": "Can you name all of your grandchildren?", "answer": "genitalia", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:31:19.255425", "question": "Can you name the person in this photo?", "answer": "sarah", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:31:33.578528", "question": "What did you do last weekend?", "answer": "i went for a walk in the park", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:31:46.102565", "question": "What\u2019s the name of your daughter/son?", "answer": "emily", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:32:05.976832", "question": "Can you describe the last time you went to the grocery store?", "answer": "no", "is_correct": true}], "final_score": 5}
{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:46:39.565274", "session_summary": [{"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:45:41.064623", "question": "Can you point to the phone in the room?", "answer": "it's on the desk", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:45:55.235704", "question": "What room are you in right now?", "answer": "brian is in the kitchen", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:46:08.245800", "question": "What\u2019s the name of your doctor?", "answer": "it's george", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:46:23.198784", "question": "Can you list the things you need before going outside?", "answer": "backpack and cap", "is_correct": true}, {"timestamp": "2025-03-22T21:46:39.500657", "question": "Tell me the steps to call someone using your phone.", "answer": "pick up the phone and call", "is_correct": true}], "final_score": 5}
